<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2013 Jacob Klinker

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->

<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
   
<string name="holy">Jesus, I praise you for being the personification of perfect holiness in a sinful world.
        God, help me possess the sensitivity to hate what you hate, to promptly recognize each of my sins today,
        to immediately repent and to live transparently before you.  </string>

    <string name="eternal">God, you have existed from everlasting to everlasting.  Give me the wisdom to live my
        life in light of eternity and to abide in you.  (Psalm 41:13; 90:2).</string>

    <string name="righteous">God, thank you for imparting the righteousness of Christ upon me (Romans 3:22).
        Holy Spirit, enable me today and every day to live in light of my position as a new creation.  Cleanse me
        and make me a slave of righteousness!</string>

    <string name="faithful">God, I praise you that you are absolutely faithful, reliable and truthful.  Give me the
        wisdom to trust you with all details of my day today, from the smallest detail to my greatest dreams.  </string>

    <string name="love">God, thank you for being absolutely loving and wanting to experience me and have me more
        fully experience you.  Today, grant me the ability to delight in all the beautiful provisions you have so
        lovingly bestowed upon me.  Psalm 36:7  How priceless is your unfailing love, O God!  People take refuge in
        the shadow of your wings.  </string>

    <string name="sovereign">God, the creator and ruler of all things in the universe, you are in control of all
        matters.  Grant me the wisdom today to trust in you sovereignty accomplishing your purposes and give me
        reminders throughout the day of my accountability to you lest I become prideful, critical, or lacking in
        reverence or contentment.  </string>

    <string name="merciful">God, I am grateful your mercies are new each morning. (Lamentations 3:22-23).  Increase
        my wisdom today that I might fear you.  Help me to live this day in the awareness of your presence.</string>

    <string name="omnipresent">God, I praise you for your continual presence and pray that I might have a more
        conscious and fully integrated enjoyment of delighting in you.  Today, grant me wisdom to walk openly,
        honestly and transparently before you. (Psalm 139)</string>

    <string name="omnipotent">God, I worship you in your awesome power and pray that you would enable me to develop
        and appropriate trust and fear of you as well as a complete dependence upon your strength for each detail of
        this day, small and great.  </string>

    <string name="omniscient">God, I am comforted to know you are there with me every moment of the day and that
        nothing in the universe is kept secret or is a mystery to you.  Help me today to walk humbly in your presence;
        to live my life openly, honestly and transparently before You and Your truth.  (Micah 6:8).</string>

    <string name="immutable">God, you are perfect in every way.  Today, let me fix my focus and efforts on you and
        your perfect desires for my life. (Psalm 90:2)\n\n
        \"Every good thing given and every perfect gift is from above, coming down from the Father of lights, with
        whom there is no variation or shifting shadow.\"  (James 1:17).</string>

    <string name="wise">God, you are the source of invaluable wisdom and provide the only basis and benchmark
        for me to possess true wisdom.  Today, give me the wisdom to see my life from your point of view, to
        select the best goals for my life, and to live skillfully before you.\n\n
        Proverbs 1:7 \"The fear of the LORD is the beginning of knowledge , but fools despise wisdom and instruction.\"
        </string>

    <string name="personable">God, thank you for revealing your divine nature in human form in Christ Jesus.  Continue
        to reveal yourself to me and give me a heart that desires to know and love you far above and beyond all other
        things.  (I Peter 1:8).</string>

    <string name="spirit">Lord, I praise you that you alone are the living water for my thirst and that your
        Spirit dwells within me.  Help me to worship You in spirit and truth, with my innermost being.
        (John 4:24; 7:38).</string>

    <string name="gracious">Today LORD, I praise you that you are gracious! Remind me to abide in your abounding
        grace, knowing it is sufficient for me deepest need.  \"Therefore let us draw near with confidence to the
        throne of grace, so that we may receive mercy and find grace to help in time of need.\"  Hebrews 4:16</string>

    <string name="good">God, you are the source of every good thing.  Let the longings and thirsts of my heart be
        completely satisfied in You.  (Psalm 16:2)  </string>

</resources>
